https://funnytimes.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy | The Funny Times
We’re living in ...
Navigation
Cartoons!
Our Cartoon Treasury
Make-your-own Cartoons …
Make-your-own Cartoons Gallery
Amusements and Diversions
Send a Funny e-Card!
Free Take-a-Break Cartoons
Editorials
Back Issues
Subscribe
SUBSCRIBE!
Cart
Returning Customer?
Search0 Items
Cartoons!
Our Cartoon Treasury
Make-your-own Cartoons …
Make-your-own Cartoons Gallery
Amusements and Diversions
Send a Funny e-Card!
Free Take-a-Break Cartoons
Editorials
Back Issues
Subscribe
SUBSCRIBE!
Cart
Returning Customer?
Who we are
Funny Times Inc. is the publisher of The Funny Times, a monthly humor publication. Our website address is: https://funnytimes.com.
What personal data we collect, and why
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Contact and payment forms
When you order Funny Times subscriptions or gifts and stuff, we collect your name, mailing address, contact information (which can include a phone number and/or email address), and information necessary for payment (credit card numbers are encrypted for safe and secure transmission, and never stored by us).
Our use of your email address and phone number is limited to processing payments and shipping publications, merchandise, and information about Funny Times including email renewal notices. This information is not made available to any third parties.
The information that you give us and information about your order may be combined with other personally identifiable information (such as demographic information and past purchase history) available from our records and other sources.
Letters to the Editor and other Communications with Funny Times
We offer features where users can submit information to us. Letters to the editor and similar submissions may be made public. Requests for service, support or information may be forwarded as needed to best respond to a specific request. We may retain e-mails and other information sent to us for our internal administrative purposes, and to help us to serve customers better.
Children
Protecting the privacy of young children is important to us. For that reason, we do not solicit, collect or maintain information from those we know are under 13.
Visitors who are under 13 years of age should ask their parent or legal guardian for assistance when using the site and should not submit any personally identifying information to the site.
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
Our website uses Google Analytics, a service which transmits website traffic data to Google servers in the United States. Google Analytics does not identify individual users or associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. We use reports provided by Google Analytics to help us understand website traffic and web page usage. Furthermore, as of June 1 2018, we anonymize all visitor IPs before sending on to Google Analytics.
Want to opt out of Google Analytics tracking on our site? Opt out of Google Analytics
For more information on Google Analytics’ privacy policy: https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html (see Section 7, Privacy)
Who we share your data with
Occasionally, we make our subscriber mailing list available to third parties for marketing purposes and to carefully screened companies offering products and services that we believe would interest our readers. If you do not want to receive these offers, please email your name and address to: info@funnytimes.com and request that we not share your name and address with third parties.
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes (for example, if you have purchased a print subscription to The Funny Times, we must retain your address-related data for as long as we are actively shipping monthly issues.)
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
The Funny Times contact information
The Funny Times
PO Box 18530
Cleveland Hts OH 44118
United States
Phone: 1-888-FUNNYTIMES (1-888-386-6984 | Toll-Free 9am to 5pm EST) Fax: 216-371-8696 | INFO@FUNNYTIMES.COM
Additional information
How we protect your data
We take your privacy seriously, and we take ongoing active measures to ensure we collect only the personal data necessary to our interactions with our visitors and customers, storing it only as long as is necessary. We do everything reasonable to maintain a secure web server environment, in order that the personal data we hold in our care remain safe.
What data breach procedures we have in place
In the event of a data breach, we will notify all visitors and customers for whom we have accurate contact information within two weeks of our first knowledge of that breach. We cannot take extraordinary measures to notify individuals or other entities who have not provided accurate contact information.
What third parties we receive data from
From time to time, The Funny Times purchases mailing lists from a range of vendors of such lists, for use in our print direct mail campaigns. We use that information only for the purposes of an individual direct mail campaign, and we do not save or store that information afterward.
Changes to Our Privacy Policy
We will revise or update this policy if our practices change, or as we develop better ways to keep you informed about them. You should refer back to this page for the latest information and the effective date of any changes. If we decide to change this policy, we will post a new policy on our site and change the date shown below. Changes to the policy shall not apply retroactively.
Questions? For any other information about our privacy policy, please contact info@funnytimes.com or call 1-888-FUNNYTIMES (1-888-386-6984).
Funny Times Privacy Policy, Version 1.02, updated June 1, 2018.
ShareClick to share on Facebook (Opens in new window)Click to share on Pinterest (Opens in new window)Click to share on Reddit (Opens in new window)Click to share on Twitter (Opens in new window)
What are you looking for?
Search for:
Any Category
Back Issues
Cartoon of the Week
Featured Articles
Featured Bonus Cartoons
Love and Hate Mail
Make-your-own Cartoons
Ray Lesser Editorials
Latest IssueFunny Times November 2020 Issue1 day agoCartoon of the WeekCartoon of the Week for October 7, 20201 day agoRay’s EditorialsPandemic Progress1 day agoWe’ve made great strides since the pandemic started in coping with our ever more surreal …more »
The Funny Times PO Box 18530
Cleveland Hts OH 44118
Phone: 1-888-FUNNYTIMES
(1-888-386-6984 | Toll-Free 9am to 5pm EST)
Fax: 216-371-8696 | INFO@FUNNYTIMES.COM
Funny Stuff by CategoryFunny Stuff by Category
Select Category
Back Issues  (158)
Cartoon of the Week  (1,268)
Featured Articles  (35)
Featured Bonus Cartoons  (71)
Love and Hate Mail  (23)
Make-your-own Cartoons  (28,561)
Ray Lesser Editorials  (226)
Hot off the presses …Funny Times November 2020 Issue1 day agoPandemic Progress1 day agoCartoon of the Week for October 7, 20201 day agoCartoon of the Week for September 30, 20201 week ago
Cartoons!
©2006-2016 Funny Times, Inc.
Type and Press “enter” to Search
OK
Reanimate your friends.
Feed brains now!
CLOSE
